

Arash Abdollahi

Frontend Developer



22612022



Arash8877@gmail.com



Askevænget 37, 1th - 2830 Virum



https://arash-site.onrender.com/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/arashab/



https://github.com/arash8877

Skills

- React
- Next.js
- TypeScript
- TanStack Query
- Redux
- tailwind

- Node.js
- Agile
- Teamwork
- Communication

Languages

- Danish PD3
- English
- Kurdish
- Farsi

Profile

Frontend developer with a keen interest in full-stack development and a background in electrical engineering. Successfully completed 15+ projects and an intensive 10-month full-stack bootcamp. Combining technical expertise with strong teamwork and interpersonal skills, I thrive in collaborative environments and excel at problem-solving. Explore my portfolio at: https://arash-site.onrender.com/

Experience

2024-Now

Frontend Developer | TrialSync

Copenhagen

Situation: The company needed to develop three distinct platforms from scratch to support business growth.

Task: I was responsible for building the frontend for all platforms.

Action: I utilized Next.js, TypeScript and Tailwind to build scalable and component-based frontends for each platform. I implemented performance and SEO optimization by:

- Uzing lazy loading to improve initial page load times.
- Leveraging TanStack Query for efficient data fetching, and caching
- Applying Next.js optimization like SSR and SSG for improve SEO

2020-2023

Self-Directed Learning. and Skill Enhancement

Virum

I independently dedicated time to self-learn web development, proactively enhancing my skills through hands-on projects, continuous learning, and staying abreast of market trends

2016-2024

Electrical Engineer | Grafisk Maskinfabrik

Birkerød

Provided technical support and developed custom scripts. Worked on embedded software and system automation.

Education

2023-2023

Full-stack web development | Hack Your Future

Copenhagen

JavaScript, React, Node.js and MySql were key components of my education, enhancing my proficiency

2013-2016

MSc in Electrical Engineering | DTU

Lyngby

Specialize in power systems as the primary focus area